Benjamin Vaughan Papers 1746-1900 Mss.B.V46p
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. General Correspondence, 1746-1952; 6.5 linear feet (Box 2-27)
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 February 26; 3 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], 1805 February 28; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 March 6; 7 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 March 6; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 March 12; 6 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 March 16; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Snow, Gideon, 1805 March 16; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 March 22; 2 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 March 22; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 March 30; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 March 31; 3 p.; Warren, J
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, [1805 ca. March]; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 April 21; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 May 1; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 May 6; 1 p.; Samuel Vaughan and son
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 May 6; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 May 6; 1 p.; Samuel Vaughan and son
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 May 7; 10 p; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 May 7, 8, June 29; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 May 8; 5 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 May 8; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 May 8; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 May 9; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ADS, receipt to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 May 9; 1 p.; Joshua Wingate and Son
  - ALS to Manning, William, 1805 May 13; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ADS, Benjamin Vaughan contract with Le Bel de Margary, 1805 May 21; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 May 22; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 May 27; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 May 28; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 May 31; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 June 5; 2 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 June 15; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 June 25; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 June 28; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 June 29; 1 p.; Joshua Wingate and Son
  - AL to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1805 June 30; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 July 4; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 July 11; 3 p.; Romilly, Samuel, Sir, 1757-1818
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 July 11; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - AL to Judge North and Judge Cony, 1805 July 22; 6 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 July 30; 2 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 July 30, [August 1]; 1 p.; Le Bel de Marguy
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 July 30; 5 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
    Includes Copy.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1805 August 5; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - AMs, Hints for the preservation of the New Academy Hall from lightning, 1805 August 6; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1735-1851, 1805 August 14; 2 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1735-1851, 1805 August 15; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1735-1851, 1805 August 15; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
    Copy included.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1735-1851, 1805 August 15; 2 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ALS to [Harvard College], 1805 August 17; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 August 17; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 August 17; 7 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 August 29; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1805 July 9; 1 p.; Parker, Daniel
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 September 1; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 September 3; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 September 14; 6 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 September 23; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 September 26; 1 p.; Darby, John
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], 1805 September 26; 1 p.; Gee, W. and A. P
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 September 28; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 October 2; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
    Concerning William Oliver Vaughan.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 October 23; 2 p.; Le Bel de Marguy
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 October 26; 2 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 November 15; 4 p.; Le Bel de Marguy
  - ALS to Montague, Ralph, 1805 December 4; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 December 5; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 December 15; 3 p.; Le Bel de Marguy
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1805 December 17; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - Miscellaneous Items to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], [ca. 1805?]; 5 p.; [Le Bel de Marguy]
  - AL to Manning, Anderson, and Bosanquet, 1805; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ADS, Check Book containing stubs only, 1805-1806; 1 item.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-, 1806 January 2; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 January 6; 3 p.; Le Bel de Marguy
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 January 15; 2 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 January 17; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], 1806 January 21; 2 p.; Le Bel de Marguy
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 January 21; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1806 January 20; 1 p.; Manning, William, 1767-1849
  - ADS, receipts to Benjamin Vaughan for the importation of wine, 1806 February 1, March 19; 2 p.
  - ALS to [?], 1806 February 7; 1 p.; Montague, Ralph
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 February 14; 2 p.; Merrill, Ezekiel
  - AL to Merrill, Ezekiel, 1806 February 18; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Collins, John, 1806 February 20; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 February 20; 6 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 February 22; 8 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
    Includes copy
  - ALS to [Vaughan, William, 1752-1850], [1806 February]; 1 p.; Collins, John
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 March 4; 3 p.; Darby, Anne
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 March 4; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Hallowell, Robert, 1806 March 5; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 March 5; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 March 5; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 March 5; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 March 6; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 March 7; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 March 8; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 March 8; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 March 10; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 March 13; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 March 28; 4 p.; H. M. B
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 April 10; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Buckminster, Joseph Stevens, 1806 April 8; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 April 18; 2 p.; Le Bel de Marguy
  - ALS to Boyd, Isabella, 1806 April 22; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 April 24; 3 p.; Boylston, Ward Nicholas
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 April 26; 3 p.; Le Bel de Marguy
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 April 29; 1 p.; Le Bel de Marguy
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 April 30; 2 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 May 13; 2 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 May 26; 1 p.; Parsons, Theophilus
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 May 29; 2 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 June 5; 2 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 June 16; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 June 19; 2 p.; Manning, William, 1767-1849
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 June 26; 2 p.; Le Bel de Marguy
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 June 26; 3 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 July 4; 5 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - AL to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1806 July 6; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-1827
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 July 13; 3 p.; Le Bel de Marguy
  - ALS to Bradford, Alden, 1765-1843, 1806 July 14; 8 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 July 15; 3 p.; Manning, William, 1767-1849
  - ALS to [?], 1806 July 15; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 July 28; 1 p.; Manning, William, 1767-1849
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 July 29; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - Als to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1806 July 29; 1 p.; Forbes, B. W
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 July 30; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 August 4; 3 p.; Le Bel de Marguy
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 August 4; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 August 5; 3 p.; Rush, Benjamin, 1746-1813
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 August 8; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1806 August 9; 5 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-1827
  - AL to [?], 1806 August 13; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Angerstein, J. J., Goldsmid, Isaac L., and Marten, R. P, 1806 August 15; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 August 22; 3 p.; McKeen, Joseph
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 August 22; 2 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 September 29; 3 p.; Abbot, Abiel, 1770-1828
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 October 6; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 October 6; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 October 14; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], 1806 October 21; 1 p.; Richards, John
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 October 22; 2 p.; Ames, Fisher, 1758-1808
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 October 22; 4 p.; Rush, Benjamin, 1746-1813
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 October 27; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 October 31; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 November 3; 3 p.; Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], 1806 November 6; 1 p.; Richards, John
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-], 1806 November 16; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1806 December 31; 3 p.; Richards, John
  - AMs, Carbonells. A new kind of paint proposed as an advantageous substitute for painting in distemper, [ca. 1806]; 2 p.
  - AL to [Collins, John], [1806?]; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AMs Charles Vaughan, bankruptcy, [1806?]; 8 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1807 January 7; 2 p.; Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1807 January 27; 3 p.; Cheverus, J
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1807 January 30; 4 p.; Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], 1807 January 30; 2 p.; Dr. Corny
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], 1807 February 8; 2 p.; Dearborn, Henry, 1751-1829
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1807 February 12; 2 p.; Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1807 February 19; 2 p.; Bradford, Alden, 1765-1843
  - ALS to Warren, Samuel, 1807 March 31; 3 p.; Warren, J
  - AL to Cabot, George, 1751-1823, 1807 April 3; 7 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Manning, William, 1807 May 4; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to [?], 1807 May 4; 14 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - Al to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1807 May 18; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1807 June 29; 2 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Benjamin, William, John, Charles, and Samuel Vaughan and John Merrick, 1807 June 30; 1 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Parsons, Theophilus, 1807 July 8; 44 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1807 July 22; 1 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-1827
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1807 August 1; 3 p.; Micheux, Andre
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1807 August 6; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1807 August 7; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-1827
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1807 August 8; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-1827
  - AL to [?], 1807 August 24; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell, 1807 August 31; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1807 September 15; 3 p.; Bird, H. M
  - AL to [Vaughan, Sarah Manning], 1807 September 27; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1807 October 4; 4 p.; Michaux, Francois André, 1770-1855
  - AL to Cabot, Henry, 1807 November 18; 185 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1807 December 4; 2 p.; North, Joseph
  - AL to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1807 December 9; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1807 December 18; 2 p.; Abbot, J
  - ADS, Minutes, 1807 December 18; 1 p.; Kennebec agricultural society
  - ALTcy to [?], [1807 December 20]; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to [?], 1807 December 22; 43 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALTcy to [?], 1807 December 22; 14 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1807 December 30; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1808 January 3; 1 p.; Davis, Daniel
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1808 January 17; 1 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-1827
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1808 January 25; 3 p.; Dearborn, Henry, 1751-1829
  - AL to [Sewall, David], 1808 February 28; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1808 March 14; 3 p.; Cony, D
  - ALS to Cony, D. and Sterne, Dr, 1808 March 15; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1808 March 22; 6 p.; Petty, H
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1808 April 5; 2 p.; Godon, Silvan
  - AL to [?], 1808 April 8; 7 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1808 April 19; 3 p.; Bagswell, Jonathan
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1808 April 14; p. 11; Gorham, John
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1808 April 29; 1 p.; Thomas Lewis and Son
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1808 May 21; 3 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1808 July 13; 2 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1808 August 2; 1 p.; Appleton, Jesse, 1772-1819
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1808 August 25; 3 p.; Ware, John
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1808 September 2; 3 p.; Michaux, Francois André, 1770-1855
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1808 October 18; 2 p.; Godon, S
  - ALS to Dr. Dillaway, 1808 December 14; 2 p.; Dr. Gorham
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1809 January 16; 3 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-1827
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1809 March 11; 3 p.; Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858
  - ADS, Perscription for Mr. William Weston's son, 1809 March 30; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to [?], 1809 July 19; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Warren, John, 1778-1856, 1809 September 27; 20 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to her relatives, [1809 September]; 4 p.; Pennefeather, Darby
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1809 October 5; 1 p.; Carter, Stanley
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1809 November 9; 1 p.; Cazeaux, Gd
  - ALS to Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1809 November 10; 3 p.; Davis, Daniel
  - ALS to Fitts, John, 1809 November 28; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Sullivan, William, 1809 December 6; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1810 January 28; 2 p.; Merrick, John, 1766-1861
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1810 March 30; 4 p.; Selectmen of Milton, Massachusetts.
  - ALS to [Freeman, James, 1759-1835], 1810 April 23; 6 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1810 May 18; 4 p.; Warren, John Collins
  - ALS to Warren, John Collins, 1778-1856, 1810 May 31; 6 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AMS, concerning the spotted fever, [1810 ca. May]; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1810 June 12; 2 p.; Jeffries, Edward
  - ADS, Prescription for Mr. Abbott, 1810 June; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1810 July 9; 1 p.; Mann, A
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], 1810 July 25; 2 p.; Coffin, Timothy Gardner
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1810 July 28; 4 p.; Warren, John Collins, 1778-1856
  - ALS to Mr. Thatcher, 1810 August 3; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Warren, John Collins, 1778-1856, 1810 August 6; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Freeman, James, 1810 August 10; 8 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AMs, Concerning the treatment of rabies, 1810 August 13; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1810 August 20; 4 p.; Freeman, James, 1759-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1810 August 21; 2 p.; Dearborn, Henry, 1751-1829
  - ALS to Gorham, John, 1810 August 23; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Freeman, James, 1810 August 25; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to [?], 1810 August 29; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1810 August 31; 2 p.; Freeman, James, 1759-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1810 September 1; 4 p.; Gorham, John
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1810 September 1; 3 p.; Warren, John Collins
  - ALS to Freeman, James, 1759-1835, 1810 September 26; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1810 October 13; 1 p.; Howell, Thomas
  - AMS, Concerning the meridian of Paris, [ca. 1810]; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1810 October 17; 2 p.; Freeman, James, 1759-1835
  - AMs, Prescription for Mr. Lovejoy and for Owen Lovejoy, 1810 October 20; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1810 October 29; 3 p.; Coleman, Mary Ann
  - ALS to Dr. Coleman, 1810 November 5; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1810 November 7; 1 p.; Lothing, Dudley
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, 1810 December 5; 3 p.; Vaughan, Lucy
  - AL to Vaughan, Sarah, 1810 December 15; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Gardiner, Robert Hallowell, 1782-1864, 1810 December 19; 2 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - AL to [?], 1810 December 22; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - Ads, Petition to the Senate and House of Representatives of Massachusettes, 1810 December 24; 4 p.; Maine Agricultural Society
  - Ad, Concerning foreign relation of the U.S. with Britain and France, [ca. 1810]; 28 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1811 April 25; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - AL to [?], 1811 May 4; 8 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to [?], 1811 May 4; 6 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to [Parsons, Theophilus, 1750-1813], 1811 June 20; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Freeman, James, 1811 August 3; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to [?], 1811 August 6; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Buckminster, Joseph Stevens, 1811 October 31; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Misses Vaughan, 1811 November 27; 4 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - AL to Gardiner, Robert Hallowell, 1782-1864, 1811 December 18; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1811 December 30; 2 p.; Appleton, Jesse, 1772-1819
  - AL to Mrs. Robert Hallowell Gardiner, 1812 January 9; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - AL to [Mrs. Robert Hallowell Gardiner], 1812 January 19; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Vaugan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1812 January 24; 3 p.; Appleton, Jesse, 1772-1819
  - ALS to [Mrs. Robert Hallowell Gardiner ?], 1812 January 31; 2 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Mrs. Robert Hallowell Gardiner, 1812 February 27; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Mrs. Robert Hallowell Gardiner, 1812 February 29; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - AL to Appleton, Jesse, 1772-1819, 1812 February; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Mrs. Robert Hallowell Gardiner, [1812?] March 8; 4 p.; Vaughan, E. Francis
  - AMs concerning the disease of Mr. Barton, 1812 March 30; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Appleton, Jesse, 1772-1819 and Dr. Cooke, 1812 April 22; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Mrs. Robert Hallowell Gardiner, 1812 May 7; 4 p.; Vaughan, Elizabeth Frances
  - ALS to Vaughan, Lucy, 1812? May 16; 3 p.; Whitwell, Lucy C
  - ALS to Vaughan, John, 1756-1841, 1812 May 25; 1 p.; Jefferson, Thomas, 1743-1826
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1812 May 31; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1812 June 2; 1 p.; Ticknor, Elisha
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1812 June 9; 4 p.; Grant, Elizabeth F. Vaughan
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Sarah Manning], 1812 July 2; 4 p.; Grant, Elizabeth F. Vaughan
  - ALS to Adams, Samuel, 1812 July 6; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1812 July 24; 4 p.; Grant, Elizabeth F. Vaughan